Zua Xiong

♦ Fresno, CA ♦ (559) 801-3720 ♦ zuaxiong469@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

An Alumni from California State University of Fresno in Spring of 2021. Experienced in office and operations management, financial accounting, and marketing in the retail industry. Able to multitask and work effectively in a fast-paced environment. I also have knowledge and experience in different ERP systems such as QuickBooks, NetSuite, Microsoft Dynamics, and Sage 500.

CORE COMPETENCIES

- Document Management Skills
- Problem-Solving Skills
- Verbal/Digital Communication Skills

- Collaborative Team Building Skills
- Data Entry/Bookkeeping
- Attentive to Detail

EDUCATION

California State University, Fresno - Fresno, CA

Bachelor of Science in Business Management (B.S.) COMPUTER SKILLS

8/2015 - 5/2021

 Advance skills in MS Dynamics, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook and QuickBooks

Ten-Key By-Touch

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

RV Jensen/Tank Specialties of California – FRESNO, CA

10/2023 - Current

BOOKKEEPING/ACCOUNTING CLERK

- Generated reports for credit card transactions daily.
- Process and file invoices from customers and vendors according to the accounting period/fiscal year.
- Direct phone calls/schedule appointments to the according party.
- Record job information through the SAGE ERP system.
- Process payments from customers.
- Record and review employee hours for pay periods.
- Request and order necessary parts for jobs.

ELITE TEAM OFFICES - CLOVIS, CA

4/2023 - 8/2023

ACCOUNTS RECEIVABLE

- Use of Microsoft programs for data entry/collections/generating invoices
- Communicate through phone calls/email daily with customers/vendors.
- Generated a step-by-step collections process for the company and legal collections letter template.

BEDROSIANS TILE & STONE - FRESNO, CA

6/2021 - 4/2023

ACCOUNTS RECEIVABLE COLLECTOR

- Use of Microsoft Software such as Excel, Dynamics, and Word daily to manage assigned accounts
- Communicate through phone calls/emails with large corporates/companies regarding past due balances
- Collect past due balances and generating payment plans to assist customers on making payments to avoid Collections Agency
- Manage over 1500 customer accounts from 13 different branches across the United States
- Conducted account reviews with customers interested in increasing credit limits and new purchases.

LANGUAGES

- Fluent in English
- Fluent in Hmong